I really want to get this off my chest.
I'm really tired of this.
This right here, sad, but this is what we voted for.
I'm tired of this from real people.
I'm tired of this from bots because this is a lie.
This is a PSYOP.
Can't believe nothing.
Because they've been frottin' and they done lied to you.
That is a lie.
You did not vote for this.
Your votes don't matter.
So often, what the government does is it creates scenarios that puts the onus on the people to futilely attempt to change things that it only has the control to change.
A great example of this is the post-civil rights movement of the 70s.
When Nixon came into power and you saw the black power movement happening and the black identity movement happening, Nixon said, okay, let me tell you what we're going to do.
And this is what they conjured up.
Now, remember, these are the post-civil rights Democrats and Republicans.
They were never not racist.
Keep listening.
So, they said, these blacks are getting really organized.
They're getting very sharp about their identity being, like, suppressed and repressed.
They're getting access to education now on, like, a higher level.
So, we need to shift their focus.
And so, what they did was they started making initiatives to bring black people into capitalism.
And the goal was to offer small groups, small bits of access that would then become beacons for what is possible.
And that turned into black excellence.
So, what it did was it alleviated the government of the expectation to correct and to provide resources that it hadn't before and put the onus on the community to somehow magically wave a wand and be able to make those corrections.
And we have been chasing our tails ever since.
We have been chasing our tails ever since because we keep hearing black people talk about financial literacy and generational wealth.
And, baby, no amount of financial literacy, generational wealth, talent, et cetera, is going to create equality.
Equality, that's what should be happening.
Equality.
You see, the thing about white people is that they have equality on a certain level.
Race on a certain level.
But class equality is not possible.
And racial equality is definitely not possible when you are black.
Period.
Because all these blacks that you see getting class equality, they still don't have racial equality, which is why Kamala Harris was never going to be president.
So, when I'm seeing all of these people thinking like, oh, we voted for this.
No, you fucking didn't.
This nation rigs every election it can get its hands on all over the world.
Why do you think it's not rigging this one?
What type of nonsensical mindset are you in that you think a nation that won't give you health care, that won't give you schooling, that is killing your people all over the place, counts your vote?
Oh, well, if our vote didn't matter, then they wouldn't work so hard to stop it.
Yes, they would.
They just want something to do.
And they hate you.
So, they'll literally do anything to piss you off and to fuck with you.
They don't need a logical, rational reason.
Quit trying to apply your logic and rationale to illogical, irrational people.
And for the record, again, you are not choosing who the president is of the United States.
Those decisions are made in Europe.
Okay?
Europeans funded the American Revolution.
Europeans funded World War II.
The United States and Israel are run by the same people.
The decisions that we here in the United States end up having to live under have trickled down from people in Europe.
And that goes the same for the Caribbean.
My people in Grenada, it's like, oh, you know, oh, we're so frustrated with the prime minister.
The prime minister?
If you want a Grenada grant, you got to go to London.
If you're in Jamaica and you want to appeal a case, you got to go to London.
We're not sovereign.
And at the end of the day, the reason why your money is safest in Switzerland is because it's base.
It's base.
Because that's where the people who run shit live.
So, I just want us to stop selling this lie.
Anytime you see someone say that's what they voted for, that's what we voted for, I want you to stop them in their tracks.
Because the narrative that voting is fair has to stop immediately.
That's why you need to stop listening to people who even suggest that voting is fair.
People like Roland Martin and Joy Reid and Angela Rye and anybody.
Anybody.
Anybody on CNN, Rachel Maddow and what's the one with the white hair, Anderson?
All of them.
They're all lying to you.
Voting is not fair, particularly on an electoral level.
Anybody who thinks that Gavin Newsom is just by accident the governor of California has lost their minds.
There's a reason why Kamala Harris was able to become the DA and then a black senator.
She married into the possibility to do that.
But y'all don't want to believe these things because you want to believe the lie that America has been telling you,
which is that you can achieve anything you want and you cannot.
You cannot achieve anything you want unless you're willing to sell your soul for certain things.
I have had to give up on many a dream because I was not going to sell my soul.
And we need to give up on the American dream because it requires us to sell our soul.